I'm Giving the Disgraced Noble Lady I
Rescued a Crash Course in Naughtiness
That bag... What exactly is in there?
Naughty = Happiness
You have a little sister
at home, do you not?
I have a big sister as well.
Did the Great Demon Lord tell you?
About the incident that
happened to the Evans family.
Yes, I heard...
about your big sister committing a huge crime—
That is not true!
My big sister can't even kill a bug.
She would never do such a thing!
I just know that rotten excuse of
a prince did it to frame my sister!
But my family chose to cut
her out of our family...
So you didn't resent your big sister?
Don't be ridiculous!
What I cannot stand is the Evans family, and...
myself because couldn't save my sister!
My sister has always been kind
to me ever since I was born.
But things changed... and
I couldn't do anything to help.
That's why I was going to
rescue her when I grew up.
But I was too late.
My sister disappeared.
Natalia...
After that incident, her
belongings were thrown away,
and the only thing left was this bag.
Thanks to this,
I can use my magic to tell that
my sister is alive somewhere.
Is that a lost article detection spell?
I've read about them.
That's right.
I don't know who it is,
but I want to crush whoever has
captured my sister with my own hands!
Why... do you assume that
your sister is in captivity?
Every time I try it, a strong
power jams my spell.
I'm sure the creep who confined
my sister is interfering with it!
HEHEHE
Who on earth could it be?
I'll find him no matter what,
and shred him to pieces!
A-Allen is going to be shred to pieces!
I will locate my sister
no matter what it takes.
And that's why I have to
become much, much stronger!
Have no fear.
You will definitely find your sister.
It's so strange.
You're pretty much a stranger I just met,
but it feels like I've
known you for a long time.
That's probably because I...
I'm so sorry, Natalia!
Ch-Chris?!
I had no idea you had such a sad past!
I am a fool! An idiot!
I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me!
Anyhow, we need to get
out of this dungeon...
Is it the magical
creature from earlier?
A salamander?!
Is this the dungeon boss?!
Charlo?!
I'll draw the attention
of this magical creature.
Please go and get Allen in the meantime.
You can't!
That's a very dangerous magical creature...
I will protect you!
Chris!
Natalia hurt her foot.
Please take her and run!
O-Okay, I will!
I can't!
I can't leave you alone, Charlo!
You need to listen to me, Natalia!
Please, Chris!
Let's go, Natalia!
It'll be fine.
I'm going to protect Natalia!
This way!
Come this way!
Charlo!
B-Big sister?!
Huh?!
Are you the one who hurt Charlotte?!
What is this amount of mana?!
This is the power of the
Great Demon Lord...!
Dad, you don't think this is...?
Yes, it can only be Allen.
I hope the school building stays intact.
Huh?!
There's no problem.
It's easy to defeat her.
G-Great Demon Lord!
Huh?!
Oh, jeez!
I said, sit!
What's going on?
Oh no, students aren't
allowed in here right now.
Only me, the magical creature
teacher, can enter.
Professor Lis!
Salamander is acting strange.
Oh my, little Pochi.
You remembered my dear Allen, did you?
He's your daddy, because he raised
you from when you were just an egg.
What?!
Charlotte, you did well.
I'm very sorry, headmaster.
It's all my fault.
I'll receive any punishment!
Hm, you seem to have grown a bit.
Great Demon Lord, I...
Come on, time for the moving reunion.
Allen, I...
Look, Natalia is worried about you.
I'm glad you're okay, Natalia.
Huh?! My glasses? And my hair?!
It's all back to normal?
So you really are...!
I'm sorry for deceiving you.
I know I must have caused
you a lot of trouble.
So I've been wanting to apologize...
My sister! You're my big sister, right?!
Yes.
Then... do you remember the book you
used to read to me when I was little?
The story about the zoo, right?
The one about children heading to the zoo.
It was somehow misplaced, so
someone must've thrown it away.
Natalia?
Is that...?
It was almost thrown away, so I hid it.
I wanted, I just wanted... for you
to read this to me one more time.
Natalia!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry that I couldn't help you!
Me too. I'm sorry I left you all alone.
I'm happy for you, mommy.
A fairy-tale ending.
Thank you for everything, Professor Allen.
Don't you mean to call me the Great Demon Lord?
We owe you a lot.
I never imagined that you'd be the savior.
That's right.
Allen saved my life, and right now
he's my precious, you know...
Your precious...?
Boyfriend, right?
These two are dating, indeed.
Huh?
N-No, we're not, Natalia.
That was just...
Wh-What's wrong?!
You fricking bastard!
What's wrong?! Everything!
So that's why I couldn't locate
my sister with my spell!
You approached her hoping
to seduce her, didn't you?!
What the hell have you done to my
precious sister, you bloody bastard!
No! That's a misunderstanding, Natalia!
Don't take it seriously!
P-Please! Somebody, stop her!
Just leave them be.
Now that we've come together,
let's go eat something good.
Yay!
I'm hungry!
We don't want to get roped in, so maybe
we'll go to the cafeteria as well.
Let me buy you dinner for causing so much trouble.
Who knew Allen and Charlotte were
faking their relationship...
I'm very disappointed.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
But it is true that they love each other.
Shredding you to pieces would be too lenient!
I'll finish you right here, right now!
So, until they are ready to tell each other
how they really feel, let's watch over them.
I'm Giving the Disgraced Noble Lady I
Rescued a Crash Course in Naughtiness
We haven't spent time like this in a while.
Indeed.
It's nice and peaceful.
It really is.
Now that we've solved the problem
and returned to the mansion,
there's one thing that's clouding my mind.
That night, why did Charlotte
want to ask me how I felt?
What were you going to say to me, Allen?
I still want to ask Allen what I
couldn't ask him the other night.
Right now, there's still time to...
You know...
Hello, nya!
Demon Lord and Lottie,
long time no see, nya!
It's been a while, Miacha.
I haven't seen you since Episode 6.
What are you doing here?
Delivering you a package, nya!
Brought to you by Miacha of
Satyros Shipping Company, nya!
Leave from the main entrance!
Allen, this package doesn't
say who it's from.
I wonder who it could be...
Is that a magic circle?
Yes. Let's see...
Allen?!
Is it summoning magic?!
Summoning...
Stay back, Charlotte!
Big sister!
How have you been, my dear sister?!
Natalia?!
But why...?
Operation: Surprise was a great success!
Yes, nya!
Eruca, Miacha, what do you
mean by Operation: Surprise?
Natalia told me she wanted
to come visit you.
I thought we should take this chance and
surprise you, so I asked Miacha to help me.
That's how it happened, nya.
Thank you for your cooperation.
So, where is the Great Demon Lord?
If he isn't around, I can have my big
sister all to myself so I wouldn't mind.
I am right here.
I see you still haven't kicked the bucket.
Then to encourage you to give up my sister,
perhaps I should take your life right now...
Wha... It's a misunderstanding!
And fighting is naughty!
Oh, you're mistaken, big sister.
This is a passionate communication
from a beloved disciple.
Who's the beloved disciple?
What nonsense.
The master of this mansion is me.
If you can't listen to
the owner of the house,
then I wouldn't mind
kicking you out by force!
Couldn't ask for anything better.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no...
I need your help!
Dorothea?!
It's been a while, Miss Charlotte!
Sorry to barge in!
D-Dorothea?
You mean the Dorothea Gri’mm Wallenstein?!
That's me.
Nya nya!
She's the very famous author who
has published a lot of novels!
I've heard of your name, too...
Man, this is making me blush.
And where is Mister Allen?
I am... right here...
It's been a while, Mister Allen.
I got a souvenir for you. My new novel.
Big sister, how do you know this novelist?
She used to live in this mansion.
Exactly.
I wrote my new novel with
the help of these two,
and it's a huge hit.
I'm hoping to write a sequel soon. Have
there been any developments since then?
Well, that's...
Developments?
And what did you come here for?
I'm in trouble!
My editor, Yor, has been relentlessly
asking about the sequel...
So I'd like for you to hide me here!
I refuse!
I don't want him breaking the wall again.
Please!
She needs your help, nya! Demon Lord!
That's right, bro!
Natalia is staying here tonight, so one
more person wouldn't make a difference.
Why do you assume that Natalia is staying?!
It's to be expected!
I must keep my eyes on you, so you won't
do anything naughty to my sister!
Natalia, you're staying here?
Let's play a lot!
It looks like it's going
to be lively tonight.
I shall cook up my secret recipe for you.
Stop organizing things
without my permission!
Gosetsu, I didn't know you could cook!
I suppose we could enjoy a dinner together.
Yes!
Where am I?
That's right.
Mother misunderstood and thought I
stole something from the house.
I'm scared, so scared.
I don't like darkness.
I don't like pain.
And being lonely is even worse.
But there's no one who will hurt me here.
I can breathe easier in here than outside.
If I can get swallowed up in
the darkness like this...
Charlotte.
Wh-Who are you?
I'm the Great Demon Lord.
I've come to take you away.
It's been a while since I last had
a nightmare from back then.
But...
Hm? What's the matter?
I couldn't stay asleep.
Are you still working, Allen?
Well, since I was working till late,
my brain is still too wound up.
You can't go to sleep?
May I stay here with you?
Sure.
Ah, this is a good chance to try that out.
What is it?
Of course it's... a naughty
thing you can only do at night.
Only at night...?
Here. It's hot, so be careful.
It smells so good.
Is this hot cocoa?
Indeed.
Let's enjoy stargazing as we drink it.
This is the naughty thing
you can only do at night?
It's wonderful!
Although I say stargazing, I
don't know much about stars.
But you know everything!
I am very familiar with the effect of
the positions of the stars on mana.
But I know next to nothing about
constellations and myths.
That sounds very much like you, Allen.
Um, the one shining in yellow is the
eye of the Spider constellation.
Below that on the right is the
constellation of the hell capybara.
Hmm...
They just look like a bunch of stars to me.
Oh!
Something sparkled!
Perhaps a shooting star?
Hm? Where?
Allen?
You don't... mind it?
No, I've never minded it, not even once.
Is that so?
Allen.
Hm?
Thank you for everything.
Drinking sweet hot cocoa as
you gaze up at the stars...
It is very naughty.
This is nothing.
Huh?
I told you that I'd give you a crash course
on all things naughty in the world.
I don't mean just this.
Recently, I'm excited for
the morning to come.
To see what kind of happy things
you're going to teach me.
I'm glad to have met you.
Put your blanket on, or you'll catch a cold.
Oh, thank you.
Allen...
Charlotte...
I know you're there, idiots!
Oh boy, you knew?!
As expected of the Demon Lord.
The heat between you two was hot enough
to forget the cold night, nya.
Whispering words of love under
a beautiful starry sky...
Master Allen sure is a tactician.
Stop monopolizing mommy just
because everyone's asleep!
Exactly!
I-I didn't mean to...!
Are you sure?
If that's the case, why are
you still holding hands?
Great Demon Lord!
I must tear your hand off so I
can remove you from my sister!
Stop being so violent!
I'll defeat Allen, too!
Mommy is mine!
Sounds good.
I shall help.
I don't even care anymore!
Bring it on!
I'll take on all of you!
I'm Giving the Disgraced Noble Lady I
Rescued a Crash Course in Naughtiness
Here's the report from our spy.
We finally have her location.
Good.
In the name of the Neruz Kingdom,
we must capture her at once.
Yes, Your Royal Highness!
Just you wait... Charlotte.